dabcc.com 2007-06-23

# Corporate Information

Saturday, June 23, 2007

DABCC Inc. Privacy Statement

* * *

DABCC values the privacy of those who visit our Web site and register for our software and services online. We think it is important for you to understand when and why we collect personally identifiable information and how we may use it. This Privacy Statement describes DABCC's data collection and use policies. Please read the entire Privacy Statement before providing any personally identifiable information to us. 

Notice 

DABCC may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, only if you provide this information to us voluntarily. The voluntary information we collect is used for internal verification to complete transactions, ensure appropriate legal use of licensed DABCC software and web services, provide notification to licensees about updates to DABCC software, and provide technical and product support to our users. DABCC may also use your name, address, and e-mail to send you marketing materials, user conference information and new product information unless you notify us that you do not want to receive these materials. Where appropriate, DABCC may pass this data to our approved DABCC Business Partners. In this event, they will also provide you the option of opting out. 

Collection 

Certain information, such as the Internet protocol address of your computer, may be stored through the use of "cookies" intended to speed access to DABCC information and services. A cookie is a short piece of data that can be used to tell us when you visit our Web sites and track your browsing habits. DABCC does not use cookies to store information such as credit card numbers, telephone numbers, or other sensitive information. A cookie is not an executable program and cannot do anything to your machine. To maintain your privacy, you can disable your browser's ability to accept cookies. 

During the installation process for certain DABCC software, information may be placed on your hard drive. This is done to enable the proper functioning of the software and ensure it is used only when properly licensed. Certain DABCC sites and software installation may require registration to gain access to special services, license keys, or other features. This information will only be used to provide support and deliver specialized services. 

DABCC also collects personally identifiable information you provide when you order and register software, data, or services; participate in e-forums, enter contests; order newsletters; register for training or conferences; or make requests that require a direct response to you. 

**Public Forums**

Dabcc.com makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Choice 

DABCC may contact you or send you marketing information about software or services unless you notify DABCC that you do not wish to receive it. You may notify us by sending an e-mail to [info@dabcc.com ](mailto:info@dabcc.com)as indicated below. Keep in mind, that you may not receive information on DABCC related valuable information as a result of your election to be removed from mailing lists. 

Other than as described in this Privacy Statement, DABCC will not disclose your personally identifiable information unless required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary (1) to conform to the edicts of the law, (2) to protect and defend the rights or property of DABCC, (3) or as part of a transfer of assets to a successor in interest. 

Except as stated herein, Dacca 's corporate policy is not to rent, sell, or otherwise permit access by third parties to databases composed of your personally identifiable information. 

Access 

DABCC will permit you to access information about you in our database by contacting [info@dabcc.com ](mailto:info@dabcc.com). If you believe any of the information is incorrect or needs updating, please advise us. We will correct our records upon verification of the requested change. If you no longer wish to receive e-mail or postal notifications about software, services, or special promotions, please let us know by sending an e-mail to us at [info@dabcc.com ](mailto:info@dabcc.com)and specifying that you do not want to receive these notifications. Please provide us with your exact name and address as well as a description of the publication or mail piece you received. We will use reasonable efforts to refrain from including you when sending marketing materials to DABCC clients by noting your election in our database. 

Security 

DABCC will take reasonable and prudent precautions to ensure that your personally identifiable data is protected against unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 

**Links**

This site contains links to other sites. DABCC, Inc is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Enforcement 

If you believe for any reason that DABCC has not followed these principles, please contact us at [info@dabcc.com ](mailto:info@dabcc.com), and DABCC will act promptly to investigate, correct as appropriate, and advise you of the correction. Please identify the issue as a Privacy Policy concern in your communication to DABCC
